<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>R on Griffin Everitt&#39;s Github Site</title>
    <link>http://griffineveritt.github.io/categories/r/</link>
    <description>Recent content in R on Griffin Everitt&#39;s Github Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://griffineveritt.github.io/categories/r/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Gambling Results</title>
      <link>http://griffineveritt.github.io/2022/05/01/gambling-results/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://griffineveritt.github.io/2022/05/01/gambling-results/</guid>
      <description>For my groups NBA betting model we took a number of factors into mind. We decided to factor in each team’s true shooting percentage, turnover percentage, offensive rebounds, defensive rebounds, three point percentage, offensive efficiency, and defensive efficiency. We figured that these metrics would give us the best shot at predicting the winners based on being a complete team. From there we decided to use cumulative means with all of those metrics and then used a support vector model to determine who was going to win.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NCAA Bracket Reaction</title>
      <link>http://griffineveritt.github.io/2022/04/04/ncaa-bracket-reaction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://griffineveritt.github.io/2022/04/04/ncaa-bracket-reaction/</guid>
      <description>My thinking going into the creation of my model for the NCAA Tournament included multiple factors that I believe make a good basketball team. I valued the importance of a complete team and I figured that would be the biggest indicator of teams who would be consistent and make a deep run in the tournament. Because of this, I decided to use adjusted offensive efficiency and adjusted defensive efficiency statistics from KenPom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I thought the Georgia Bulldogs would win the 2022 CFP</title>
      <link>http://griffineveritt.github.io/2021/12/03/why-the-georgia-bulldogs-will-win-the-2022-cfp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://griffineveritt.github.io/2021/12/03/why-the-georgia-bulldogs-will-win-the-2022-cfp/</guid>
      <description>The Georgia Bulldogs have proven all season that they stand in a league of their own. They have blown out opponents week after week and are yet to be truly challenged heading into the SEC championship at 12-0 against the Alabama Crimson Tide.
We are going to take a look at some data from the 2021 season and find out if the Bulldogs are ever going to be challenged or if we should just hand them the National Title right now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Should Barry Bonds be a hall of famer?</title>
      <link>http://griffineveritt.github.io/2021/10/30/should-barry-bonds-be-a-hall-of-famer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://griffineveritt.github.io/2021/10/30/should-barry-bonds-be-a-hall-of-famer/</guid>
      <description>Putting the steroids aside.. Barry Bonds had a pretty impressive MLB career. One that accounted for 7 MVP’s, 14 all-star games, 8 gold gloves and 12 silver sluggers.
It would probably be safe to say that any player with those kind of accolades, who didn’t take steroids, would be voted in to the hall of fame. But we are going to look at how dominant Bonds was and how he compares to current Hall of Fame inductees.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
